Did we get paper towels?
我們買了紙巾嗎？
You mean the thing we went to the store for?
你是指我們打算 去店裡買的東西嗎？
Nope.
沒有
Hey, I got you a present!
我幫你們準備了一份禮物
Oh, my goodness, where did you hide it?
天啊，你把它藏在哪裡？
I ordered it for your wedding and it's finally here!
我訂了它當做你們結婚的禮物 它終於送來了
You didn't have to get us anything..
你不必送我們任何…
I love it! It's huge! Let's open it!
我喜歡它，它很大，我們打開它吧
-It's a Ms. Pac-Man machine! -Oh, my God!
-是小精靈的電動 -我的天啊
I didn't know where to put it.
我不知道該把它放到哪裡去
-We can put it in the guest bedroom. -Yeah, okay.
-我們可以把它放在客房 -好吧
I kind of like it here.
我喜歡把它放在這裡
Do you like it?
你喜歡它嗎？
I practically spent my entire childhood at the arcade.
我小時候 都待在遊樂場裡
-This was my second favorite. -What's your first?
-這是我第二喜歡的遊戲 -你最喜歡什麼？
-I don't remember the name. -Well, what did it do?
-我記不得它的名字了 -它的內容是什麼？
You'd put a quarter in, pull some handles and win a candy bar.
把銅板放進去 一拉把手，就能拿到糖果
A vending machine?
自動販賣機？
Don't feel bad for me. I won every time!
別為我難過 每次我都會贏
The One Where Joey Dates Rachel
本集播出：喬伊跟瑞秋約會
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I'm so glad you guys are here.
我很高興你們都在
Guess what happened in the paleontology department.
猜猜古生物系 發生了什麼事
Do you think he saw us, or can we still slip out?
你覺得他看到了我們 還是我們有機會落跑？
Professor Newman, the department head, is retiring, so..
系主任諾曼教授 要退休了，所以…
-They made you head of the department! -I'm teaching his advanced class!
-他們讓你當系主任 -我要教他的高級課
Why didn't I get head of the department?
我為什麼沒有當上系主任？
Great. You've always wanted to teach an advanced class.
太棒了 你一直想教高級課
No, I know. It's really exciting. This is the break I've been waiting for.
不，我知道，它真的很棒 這是我一直在期待的機會
I'm not sure a court-ordered detox program..
我相信強制抗過敏排毒計劃…
was the break Professor Newman was waiting for.
不是諾曼教授 在等待的機會
But, hey.
但是…
Hey, Rach, I got a big date. Do you know a good restaurant?
瑞秋，我有個重要約會 你知道哪家餐廳不錯嗎？
Paul's Cafe. It's got great food and it's really romantic.
保羅咖啡廳，那裡東西好吃 氣氛真的很浪漫
Great, thanks.
太棒了，謝謝
Then take her to the Four Seasons for drinks.
帶她到四季飯店喝東西
Or go downtown and listen to some jazz.
或是到城裡聽爵士樂
Or dancing. Oh, take her dancing!
或跳舞，帶她去跳舞
You sure are naming a lot of ways to postpone sex.
你真的很會拖延性愛遊戲
I miss dating. Dressing up, going to a fancy restaurant.
我想念約會的感覺 盛裝打扮去好餐廳吃飯
I won't be able to do that for so long. And it's so much fun.
我很久都無法再那麼做了 那真的很有趣
Not that sitting around worrying about giving birth isn't fun.
我不是說坐在這裡 擔心生產的事不好玩
Hey, you know what? Why don't I take you out.
知道嗎？我們為什麼不去約會？
You don't want to date a pregnant lady.
你不想跟孕婦約會
Yes, I do. We're gonna have a good time.
我想我們會玩得很開心
I'll take your mind off of childbirth, and C-sections..
我會讓你忘了生孩子剖腹生產…
and baby heads stretching out..
寶寶的頭擴大了…
Okay, I'll go with you.
好吧，我答應你
-It will be fun. -All right.
-那會很好玩的 -好吧
No, no! Yes!
不，太棒了
Would you look at that.
快來看
I knocked off all your top scores. How sad.
我打敗了你的最佳成績 太慘了
Okay, I'm next.
好吧，輪到我了
Don't start another game. I'm next! Phoebe?
別再開始 輪到我了，菲比
Sorry, I couldn't hear you over all the winning.
抱歉，我贏得太開心 聽不到你說話
-Phoebe's hogging the game. -It's a stupid game.
-菲比在霸佔遊戲 -那是個愚蠢的遊戲
You think it's stupid because you suck.
你覺得它蠢 因為你很遜
I don't suck. It sucks.
我不遜，它才遜
You suck.
你很遜
If this game is gonna cause problems, I should keep it.
如果這遊戲會引起你們的困擾 我應該留下它
No, I love it. It is a great present.
不，我喜歡它，它是很棒的禮物
Why don't you go home and wait for the thank-you card?
你為什麼不回家等謝卡呢？
-Why do you want to play this game? -It doesn't spit out a Clark Bar.
-你為什麼要玩這個遊戲？ -它不會吐出糖果
Okay. Phoebe, that's it. Out of the chair.
好吧，菲比，夠了 快下來
Phoebe! Chandler!
菲比，錢德
No, no. This is a girl fight. I'm hoping it will turn into love-play.
不，這是女孩的戰爭 我希望你們能互敬互愛
Okay, look. Honey, I'm sorry..
好吧，聽著 我很抱歉…
I'm acting hostile. I don't mean to. It's just that I love this game so much..
我太凶了，我不是故意的 我真的很喜歡這個遊戲…
that I would just like the chance to play it too.
我也想玩玩它
Wow, it's amazing how well I can play with you yapping around my head..
太神奇了，你在我耳邊 像吉娃娃一樣叫個不停…
like a Chihuahua.
我還是能玩
All right, that's it. Chandler, help me get her out of the chair.
好吧，我受夠了，錢德 幫我把她拉下來
Chandler, come on.
錢德，快點
Joey, could you get that?
喬伊，麻煩你去開門
Joey.
喬伊
I thought you were in your room.
你這是幹嘛？ 我以為你在房裡
I'm picking you up for our date. For you.
我是來接你的 這是送你的
Lilies. They're my favorite. Thank you.
百合花，它們是我最喜歡的花 謝謝
And a brownie.
還有蛋糕
Well, half a brownie.
只有一半
Actually, it's just a bag.
事實上它只剩袋子
It's a long walk from the flower shop and I felt faint, so..
從花店走回來真的很遠 我覺得頭暈，所以…
This is so great! I actually feel like I'm on a real date.
這真的是太棒了 我覺得好像真的在約會
But I have morning sickness and I have on underwear that goes up to..
但我會害喜 我穿的內褲褲頭高到…
there.
這裡
Hey, come on. This is a real date.
少來了，這是真的約會
So nice place you got here.
你家好漂亮
Football. Pizza box.
桌上足球，披薩盒
Oh, a subscription to Playboy. My kind of woman.
還有花花公子雜誌 你是我喜歡的那種女人
That's my roommate's.
那是我室友的雜誌
I'd like to meet him. He sounds like a standup guy.
我想見見他 他似乎是個好男人
He's protective of me, so you'd better watch yourself.
他很保護我 你最好小心一點
Your roommate, is he good-looking?
你室友很帥嗎？
Must be tough to keep your hands off him.
你一定很努力控制自己 不愛上他
I'm pretty sure he's gay.
我相信他是男同志
No! No, he's not! Why are you trying to ruin the game?
不是的 你為什麼要毀了這個遊戲？
Which brings us back to Greely's Theory of Dominance.
這讓我想起葛瑞利的骨牌理論
That's it for today.
今天到此為止
Does anyone know where the Freeman Building is?
有人知道費利曼樓在哪裡嗎？
It's the new building on Avenue A.
那是A大道的新大樓
That's across town. I'm teaching there in 10 minutes.
它在城裡的另一邊 我10分鐘內得趕到那裡上課
Dude, that's not gonna happen.
那是不可能的
Move it! Move it!
快閃開
Hey! I'm the teacher!
我是老師
Hello.
哈囉
Sorry I'm a little late. Whoa, a lot late.
抱歉我遲到了 我嚴重遲到
Well, let me start by introducing myself.
我從自我介紹開始吧
I'm Professor Geller.
我是蓋勒教授
So to sum up..
總而言之…
I'm Professor Geller. Good job today.
我是蓋勒教授 今天大家做得很好
-What comes with the filet mignon? -Steamed vegetables.
-菲力牛排搭配什麼？ -蒸蔬菜
Instead of the vegetables..
除了蔬菜…
is there any way that I could substitute the..
我可以用什麼東西搭配…
three-pound lobster?
三磅的龍蝦？
You know what? Bring her both.
知道嗎？幫她把兩道菜都送上來
And I'll have the same.
我要點跟她一樣的東西
Wow, this is shaping up to be a pretty good date.
這真的是個很棒的約會
I almost forgot. I didn't pay you the rent.
我差點忘了 我沒給你房租
No roommate stuff. It's a date.
別當我們是室友，我們在約會
Wow, so I get to see what Joey Tribbiani is like on a date.
我想知道喬伊崔比亞尼 怎麼跟女人約會
Have any moves?
你有什麼招數？
No, I'm just myself, and if they don't like me for..
不，我只會做我自己 如果她們不喜歡我…
I'm sorry, I couldn't even get through that.
抱歉 我無法想像那種事
I knew it. Tell me your moves.
我就知道，告訴我你有什麼招數
All right.
好吧
Well..
嗯…
I start by having a bottle of wine sent to my table from a fan.
我會假裝有影迷送一瓶紅酒給我們
Oh, my God. And that works?
天啊，有用嗎？
If you add, "This is embarrassing. I just want to have a normal life."
你得加上「這真是太不好意思了 我只想過正常人的生活」
You poor little famous man.
你們這些可憐的名人
Okay, how about this one?
好吧，這個呢？
I was gonna wait until the end of the night to kiss you..
我本來想等到送你回家再吻你…
but you're just so beautiful, I don't think I can.
但你真的太美了 我想我做不到
Oh, my God!
天啊
Wow, that was fantastic! I almost leaned in. Really.
那真的太棒了 我差點就被你騙了
So tell me one of your moves.
告訴我你用的是什麼招數
All right.
好吧
So where'd you grow up?
你是在哪裡長大的？
That's your move?
那就是你的招數？
Boy, Rach, you're lucky you're hot.
瑞秋，還好你長得很美
-Come on, just answer the question. -Queens.
-快回答我的問題 -皇后區
Were you close to your parents?
你跟父母親近嗎？
-With my mom. Not so much my dad. -Why not?
-我跟媽媽親，跟爸爸不太說話 -為什麼？
I don't know. There's just this distance.
我不知道 我們之間有距離
We both try to pretend it's not there, but it is.
我們都假裝沒有 但事實上不然
It's gotta be rough.
那一定很辛苦
Yeah, it's really tough. Sometimes I think..
對，那真的很辛苦 有時候我認為…
Wow!
哇
Nice move!
太帥了
-"Where'd you grow up?" So simple. -Thank you.
-「你在哪裡長大的？」，太簡單了 -謝謝
Now, excuse me. I'm gonna use the restroom.
對不起，我要去洗手間
-Now you're watching me walk away. -Yes, I am! So simple!
-你正看著我走開 -沒錯，太簡單了
-You won't believe what I did today. -Clearly not shower or shave.
-你一定不相信今天我做了什麼 -很明顯地你沒洗澡或刮鬍子
I played this all day, and now I rule.
我玩了這玩意一整天 現在我是第一名
They should change the name to "Ms. Chandler."
他們應該把它改名為 「錢德小姐」
Although, I hope they don't.
還是不要好了
You stayed home and played Ms. Pac-Man while I went to work like a chump?
你待在家裡玩小精靈 我出門像牛一樣在工作？
I got the top 1 0 scores. I erased Phoebe off the board. High-five!
我包辦了前10名 把菲比給擠掉了，慶祝一下吧
What is the matter with your hand?
你的手是怎麼了？
I played for eight hours.
我打了八小時的電動
It'll loosen up. Check out the scores.
它會放鬆的，看看我的記錄
Also, look at the initials. They're dirty words.
看看我編的名字 它們全是髒話
-Chandler, why would you do that? -Because it's awesome.
-錢德，你為什麼要那麼做？ -因為它很棒
You think it's clever?
你覺得那麼做很聰明？
They only give you three letters, so after A-S-S, it is a challenge.
我只能寫下三個字母 除了屁股外，其他的名字可是個大挑戰
But clearly you're up to the task.
但你全都想出來了
-This one's not dirty. -Put it together with that one.
-這不是髒話 -把它跟那個連在一起
Oh.
喔
If you don't clear this off, you won't get one of those from me.
如果你沒辦法把它清掉 我不會答應你的
Ben's coming over tomorrow. This can't be there.
班明天會過來 不能讓他看到這個
-He won't know what they mean. -He's 7, not stupid.
-他不知道它們的意思 -他七歲了，他不笨
-Have you talked to him lately? -I'm gonna unplug it.
-最近你跟他談過嗎？ -我要把插頭拔掉
I'll have nothing to show for my day. Like work.
我沒辦法證明我今天做了什麼 就跟我的工作一樣
No!
不
Hey, look! It's still there!
你看，畫面還在
This thing must have some kind of primitive ROM chip!
這玩意一定是用 原始的記憶晶片
Wow. The dirty words and the computer talk.
你會說髒話 又懂電腦
This is just the coolest you've ever been.
這是你做過最酷的事
-You gotta beat your scores. -With the claw?
-你得打敗自己的成績 -我的手指都張不開了
Fine, I'll do it. We gotta get this off.
好吧，讓我來 我們得把這個消掉
Carol's still upset that you taught him "Pull my finger."
卡蘿還在氣 你教他「拉我的手指」
Pull my finger. My hand is messed up!
拉我的手指，我的手毀了
-I am not gonna answer that. -Oh, come on. Just pick one.
-我不會回答那個問題 -來吧，快挑一個
Between Monica, Phoebe, Chandler and Ross..
在摩妮卡，菲比 錢德跟羅斯之間…
if you had to, who would you punch?
如果你非那麼做不可 你會打誰？
We're friends. I wouldn't punch any of them.
我們是朋友，我不會打他們
Chandler?
錢德嗎？
Yeah, but I don't know why.
對，但我不知道為什麼
-I'm having a wonderful time! -Me too!
-我玩得很開心 -我也是
-This is the best date I ever had. -I know!
-這是我最棒的約會經驗 -我知道
I laughed so hard. Did you see the wine come out my nose?
我笑得好厲害 你看到酒從我鼻子噴出來嗎？
Joey, I think everybody saw it.
喬伊，我想大家都看到了
I never knew I could enjoy the non-sex part of a date so much.
我不知道我會這麼喜歡 沒有性愛的約會
That's because you have never been on a date with me before.
那是因為 你沒有跟我約會過
All right. Now don't judge me.
好吧，別批評我
I normally wait till my date leaves, but I'm ripping into the swan.
通常我會等我的對象離開了再這麼做 但我真的餓壞了
Okay, then you don't judge me.
好吧，你也別批評我
I'm gonna suck on the cellophane from that brownie.
我要去舔蛋糕的包裝紙
Oh, yeah.
對
So tell me, what are Joey Tribbiani's end-of-the-night moves?
告訴我喬伊崔比亞尼 說晚安的招數是什麼
Well, if I want the girl to kiss me..
如果我要那個女孩吻我…
first, I make my lips look irresistible.
首先我會讓我的嘴巴 看起來難以抵抗
How do you do it?
你都是怎麼做的？
Now you can't tell anyone, but..
你不能告訴任何人，但是…
I put on shiny lip balm.
我會塗上護唇膏
-Oh, my God. -Like a moth to a flame, I tell you.
-天啊 -女人就跟飛蛾撲火一樣
-Okay, now you go. -No, I don't want to tell you.
-好吧，輪到你了 -不，我不想告訴你
-Why not? -It's embarrassing.
-為什麼？ -那太丟臉了
More embarrassing than shiny raspberry lip balm?
比塗覆盆子口味的護唇膏 還丟臉？
I didn't say raspberry before, did I?
我剛剛沒說覆盆子口味吧？
Just tell me, Rach. Just tell me.
快告訴我，瑞秋
Okay.
好吧
All right, stand up.
站起來
Well, when we're at the door..
我們走到門邊時…
I lightly press my lips against his.
我會將我的嘴唇 輕輕壓在他的嘴唇上
Then move into his body, just for a second.
將身體靠向他 一秒鐘
And then I make this sound:
然後我會發出這樣的聲音
It doesn't sound like anything, but it works.
聽起來沒什麼 但很有效
Oh, yeah. That would work, yeah.
對，那的確有效
All right, I gotta go to bed. I had such a wonderful time.
好吧，我得睡了 我玩得很開心
Me too.
我也是
You were 50 minutes late? Did you crawl?
你遲到了50分鐘？ 你是用爬的嗎？
No, I ran, okay? It's really far.
不，我用跑的，那真的很遠
When did people stop understanding "Get out of my way"?
人們什麼時候開始聽不懂 「別擋我的路」？
Why didn't you take a cab?
你為什麼不搭計程車？
With the traffic and one-way streets, it'd take me twice as long.
塞車太嚴重，那是單行道 搭計程車得花兩倍的時間
And I have class three times a week. Who am I, Rockefeller?
我一星期有三堂課 我是洛克菲勒嗎？
You won't be able to keep doing this.
你沒辦法再繼續下去
If I don't, they'll take the class away from me.
我不那麼做 他們會取消我這堂課
And I put it in my family newsletter.
我把它登在我家的通訊報上
-Your what? -You've seen it, The Geller Yeller.
-什麼？ -你看過的，蓋勒通訊報
Right. Wow.
對
I figured out a faster route. I'm sure I can make it this time.
我想出一條比較快的路線 我想這次我能及時趕到
I just can't be afraid to get a little bit hit by cars.
我不能害怕 被車子撞到
-Hey. -Hi!
-嘿 -嗨
Remember when we talked about Cujo?
還記得我們談過《狂犬驚魂記》嗎？
I can't believe you haven't seen Cujo.
我不敢相信你沒看過《狂犬驚魂記》
Relax, it isn't Citizen Kane.
別緊張，它不是《公民凱恩》
Have you ever sat through Citizen Kane?
你看完了《公民凱恩》？
Yeah, it's really boring. But it's, like, a big deal.
對，它真的很無聊 但它是名片
Anyway, I was thinking about renting Cujo.
總之，我想去租《狂犬驚魂記》
Well, let's do it tonight.
我們今晚一起看吧
-Don't you have that big date? -Oh, right.
-你不是有約會嗎？ -對
-Hey, Joey, can I ask you something? -Yeah.
-喬伊，我能問你一件事嗎？ -問吧
After our date, did you feel weird?
昨晚約會後你覺不覺得怪怪的？
Oh, my God. You did too? It freaked me out. What was that?
天啊，你也是嗎？ 我嚇壞了，那是什麼？
I don't know. I'm kind of thinking it was the lobster.
我不知道 我想應該是龍蝦的問題
Oh, yeah. Yeah, the lobster.
對，龍蝦
-I was up sick all night. -Me too. All night.
-我吐了一整晚 -我也是
Really? We didn't cross paths.
真的嗎？我沒看到你
Yeah, well, that's because..
對，那是因為…
I stayed in my room.
我都待在房裡
You don't want to look in my hamper.
你不會想看我的洗衣籃的
Okay, I got that.
我懂了
I'll escape there. I'll come back here.
我要逃離那裡 回到這裡
All right. Come on, Ms. Pac-Man.
來吧，小精靈
Well, you're just a little bitch, aren't you?!
你是個混蛋，對吧？
Hey, you guys?
大家好
I'm sorry that I was hogging the game before.
抱歉之前 我霸佔著電動玩具
But if you don't get off soon, I will cut you.
如果你不快下來，我會殺了你
Oh, my God! Your friends have some unfortunate initials.
天啊，你朋友名字的縮寫真難聽
They're all Chandler.
那都是錢德干的
Chandler couldn't get this good.
錢德不可能有這麼厲害
I did. But it came at a price.
我很厲害，但那是要付出代價的
Ben's coming, and he can't see this.
班要過來，他不能看到這個
By age 7, kids have already seen orgies.
七歲的孩子應該都看過雜交
Was it just me?
還是只有我而已？
So..
總之…
we're about out of time.
我們沒時間了
Now, I know I've given you a lot of new information.
我知道我提供你們很多新資訊
And it may seem a little overwhelming.
那或許很嚇人
But, if there's one thing..
但今天…
you need to take away from class today..
在課堂上 你們得學會一件事…
it's that..
那就是…
dinosaurs ain't never coming back.
恐龍永遠都不會復活
I'll see you next time.
下次再見
Yes, I made it! I'm on time!
我辦到了，我及時趕到
Okay, why don't we all..
好了，請大家…
open our books to page 23..
翻到第23頁…
where..
你們…
where you will see..
你們將會看到…
a bunch of red spots.
很多紅點
Okay, why don't you all start to read while I..
請大家先看一下 我要…
This is so embarrassing.
這真的是太不好意思了
I just want to have a normal life.
我只想過正常人的生活
Wow, that's an expensive bottle of wine.
那瓶紅酒很貴的
It is?
是嗎？
That's funny, my fans don't normally do that.
真有趣 通常我的影迷不會那麼做
Are you all right? You seem a little distracted.
你沒事嗎？ 你似乎有點心不在焉
No, no, I'm fine. It's just..
不，我沒事，我只是…
Hey, can I ask you something?
我能問你一件事嗎？
Have you ever looked at someone you know..
你有沒有這樣的經驗 看著你認識的人…
and suddenly seen them in a different way?
突然間有不一樣的感覺？
You mean like from behind?
你是說從背後看嗎？
Yeah. That's exactly it.
沒錯，就是那樣
I saw this guy from behind, and he seemed totally normal.
我從背後看這個傢伙 覺得他真的很普通
And then he turned around and it was Stephen Baldwin!
他一轉身 我才知道他是史蒂芬鮑德溫
Yeah.
對
So you know exactly what I mean.
你完全瞭解我的意思
Totally! Wow.
沒錯
-Would you excuse me? -Sure.
-對不起 -請便
-Phoebe! You're on fire! -I know!
-菲比，你真的很厲害 -我知道
You can do it!
你辦得到
-Don't touch me! -Don't touch her!
-別碰我 -別碰她
Go left! Go right! Go right!
左邊，右邊，右邊
I can't! I can't!
我辦不到
No! You son of a..
不，你這個天殺的…
Phoebe?!
菲比
Oh, hi, Ben. No, don't look at the machine!
嗨，班 不，別看機器
Thank God you're home! I'm watching Cujo.
謝天謝地你回來了 我在看《狂犬驚魂記》
-Alone? -Yes! What is wrong with this dog?
-你一個人？ -對，這隻狗是怎麼了？
Did you get to the part where Cujo throws himself at the car?
你看到庫裘 自己去撞車的那一幕了嗎？
No, seriously, what's wrong with the dog?
不，真的 這隻狗是怎麼了？
Wait, what happened to your date?
等一下，你不是去約會了嗎？
Oh, it didn't work out.
我們之間不來電
-Want to watch the rest of the movie? -Oh, okay. Yeah.
-你要跟我一起把電影看完嗎？ -好吧
I never thought I'd say this..
我沒有想過我會這麼說…
but I hope this dog dies.
但我希望這隻狗死掉
What are you doing? Sit here. Protect me.
你在做什麼？ 坐在這裡保護我
Oh. Sure, yeah. Why not?
沒問題，有何不可呢？
Okay.
好吧
-That's him, that's him! That's Cujo! -I know.
-那就是他，那就是庫裘 -我知道
It's gonna be okay.
沒事的
Oh, my God. What's he gonna do now? I can't watch.
天啊，他現在會怎麼做？ 我不敢看
How can you watch this? Aren't you scared?
你怎麼能看這個？ 你不害怕嗎？
Terrified.
我怕極了
So is everybody here? I got here a little early, myself.
大家都來了嗎？ 今天我提早到了
Let us begin.
開始上課吧
Now, the hadrosaurids have been unearthed in two main locations.
海德羅恐龍 主要分佈在兩個地方
Here..
這裡…
and..
跟…
here.
這裡
Now, as for the hydrosaurs..
至於水龍…